Brother, if you start your vehicle, whether it is new or
old, it is very important for you to have some documents.  The
RC, DL or draw of the vehicle is also the driver, the person
driving the vehicle, the insurance of the vehicle
and apart from this the pollution.
Regarding pollution, I had already made a video
on my channel about Hunter 350 in which I had got the
pollution done.  Was there some process?   It was
very simple and sorted.
I showed that to all of you.  But just a few
days ago I got a
call regarding insurance.  From where I
purchased the car.  They have the details.
So it was about to expire.
Before that they had called me 5-7 days ago.
So that's what I'm going to get done today.
So that's why I thought I'd share with you guys what some of the
costing
is.  If you also own a car like HT 350
or are thinking of buying one, then the
maintenance cost
also includes the insurance cost, so
how much does it cost?  So let's go
to the service center now.  Is it going to cost anything
?  Is the process going to last?  Let's
talk about all of them.  Let's go and I have one more
thing to get done.
I also need to get this number plate changed.  So that is why it is
very
important to get that done because it was broken.  So let's get that done now
too.
Nor had I received the
soft copy of the vehicle.
But now I have got the hard copy to
show you.  So look, your
hard copy has arrived, inside which it is
written that I have taken insurance from ICICI LBR.  The
rest of the basic details of the vehicle are also written above, like
who is the manufacturer, etc.  Apart from this,
these people have also given me the ID of the vehicle number 126
under this insurance.  Apart from this,
basic details like hunter etc. are written here.
Here I also have the engine number and chassis number
etc. which I cannot show
you.  You shouldn't show it either.  The 2023
vehicle is in manufacturing.  Apart from this,
here you have a basic premium of Rs 59.
But because I have taken zero depth
₹1261.  You should take this.  Because if the
car faces any problem tomorrow.
Suppose if you suffer a total loss then you will
get this much in full.  And if you have taken the add-on of invoiced then it will be for the amount for which
you had purchased.
Like, if I have made a purchase of Rs 185, I will
get the full amount.  But I have taken zero depth.
So if tomorrow I face any problem with my car, I will have to
pay only the basic premium.  Meaning basic
premium means file charges.
Everything else ICIC LB beer will do.  Rest it costs Rs.
2372 after adding GST etc. and
I had bought the car from Wonder Motors
because friend, the
process is smooth because they have a
tie up so they get it done easily,
you just have to go and park the car, so
brother I have come after getting the insurance of my Hunter done
etc. and what other
costing has come, let's talk about it and
I have got the number plate done, okay let's
talk, it looks like this here,
you had seen it earlier, it was a bit broken, it was
broken from this place, hence I had to get
this frame actually installed new
so that now the look is fine and it was
also making noise.  That's why I got
that thing fixed so that when he used to
sit at the back, he used to get disturbed.  Let's
talk about the costing of insurance, it cost
me Rs 2372.  I don't know, last year it was
around ₹2100.  But this year
the pricing has increased a bit.  He
said that since the claims have increased, the
pricing of vehicle insurance has also increased.  If we
talk about their service, it was
decent.  Meaning there were
not many things.  Only Aadhar card was
asked for.  That work has been done by him.   The
rest was worth something like 2100 last year.
Before that it had come included with the car.
Whatever I had paid on QS,
₹1,85,000 to Royal Enfield was included in it.  The
vehicle will have to be insured every year
if you want to have zero deps.   The
overall experience of the rest of the car is quite
good.  You can check out my channel
for this car and if you want to
see any other content then let me know by commenting.  Thank you so much
for watching the